<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Champion11</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav_drawer">NavDrawerActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="error">ERROR</string>
    <string name="success">SUCCESS</string>
    <string name="alert">ALERT</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="welcome_header">Welcome to Champion 11</string>
    <string name="staking_text">Start Staking</string>
    <string name="tncTxt">Champions11 is a digital sports platform that provides an opportunity for fans to connect with each other through fantasy sports. Participation in the Champions11 Contest will be as per the terms and conditions given on the Champions11 App / Web site. There are elements of financial risk in this game and it can take getting used to. Please play responsibly and at your own risk. This advertisement is not directed to areas in which such ser vices are prohibited by law. Terms and conditions apply. Only persons 18 years of age and older can participate in the game.</string>
    <string name="privacy_txt">This document explains how Champions11 collects, processes, stores and/or shares any personal data and/or information from users (jointly re ferred to as "Information"). By accessing and/or using the Services you consent the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns about pro viding data, or having it used in any manner per mitted in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Services. As set out in the terms and condi tions relating the Services (the "Terms"), you must be at least at legal age (minimum age of 18 years) to access and/or use the Services, or if legally pos sible, to access with your legal guardian consent, due authorization and agreement with these Pri vacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="privacy_txt_info">Champions11 and/or third parties, including but not limited to business partners, advertising net works, analytics or search information providers, may collect and process the following data about you: information that you provide when you fill in</string>
    <string name="about_us_txt">Champion 11 also has daily contests and leader boards running where the users can win cash by stacking numbers daily.\n\nChampion 11 is a online app game where you will.\n\nStack on multiple numbers.\n\nChampion 11, India\'s biggest fantasy sports platform with 10 Thousand+ users playing numbers.</string>

</resources>